Guide to the David Ottenstein Photographs of Iowa
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
David Ottenstein Photographs of Iowa.
2004-2010
WA Photos Folio 82
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
2.66
(32 boxes)
Ink jet print photographs that document the transformation of the Iowa countryside from traditional family farms to industrial farmsteads, as well as the growth of agricultural industries in the American Midwest, 2004-2010. The images document traditional farmhouses, barns, silos, corn cribs, sheds and other farm buildings. They detail the physical changes of the natural and built landscape that accompany the social and economic trends at the turn of the of twenty-first century in the American Midwest. The collection includes some images of Illinois.
Ottenstein, David
General note
Title devised by cataloger.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from David Ottenstein Photography on Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana and Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2007-2010.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
David Ottenstein (born 1960)
David Ottenstein graduated from Yale College in 1982 with a degree in American Studies and a concentration in Photography. Ottenstein has worked as a free-lance photographer based in New Haven, Connecticut.
Scope and Contents
Ink jet print photographs that document the transformation of the Iowa countryside from traditional family farms to industrial farmsteads, as well as the growth of agricultural industries in the American Midwest, 2004-2010. The images document traditional farmhouses, barns, silos, corn cribs, sheds and other farm buildings. They detail the physical changes of the natural and built landscape that accompany the social and economic trends at the turn of the of twenty-first century in the American Midwest. The collection includes some images of Illinois.
Arrangement
Organized into one series: I. Photographs.
Agriculture -- Illinois -- Pictorial works; Agriculture -- Iowa -- Pictorial works; Farms -- Illinois -- Pictorial works; Farms -- Iowa -- Pictorial works; Illinois -- Pictorial works; Iowa -- Pictorial works; Middle West -- Pictorial works; Inkjet prints; Photographic prints; Ottenstein, David
- Photographs, 2004-2010; Series I; 2.66; (32 boxes)
  Arrangement
  Series I is organized into two subseries: 11" X 17" Prints and 16" X 20" Prints
  - 11" X 17" Prints
    Arranged chronologically by capture date and then alphabetically by title.
    - 2004
      - Alden Quarry, 2004, printed 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Anita Grain Elevator, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Barn Doors, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Barn Interior, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Buss Farmhouse #3, 2004, printed 2008 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Buss Farmhouse #4, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Buss Farmhouse #5, 2004, printed 2008 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Corn Crib, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Farm Tools, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Fence, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Iowa Hills, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Irwin Grain Elevator, 2004, printed 2009 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Ladora Savings Bank #3, 2004, printed 2008 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Ladora Savings Bank #4, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Long Branch Farm, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Roller Coaster, 2004, printed 2009 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Shed With Horses, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Steenhusen Farm, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Steenhusen Farm #3, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Stone Farmhouse #2, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Stone Farmhouse #3, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Stone Farmhouse #5, 2004, printed 2008 (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - Train Trestle #1, 2004, printed 2008 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Whispering Pines, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Windmill, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - 2005
      - 1954 International L-180, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Ash Tree Near Killduff, Iowa, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Boge Shed Interior #1, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - Broken Willow, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 3, Folder 29)
      - Cemetery - Elkport Lutheran Church, Elkport, Iowa, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 3, Folder 30)
      - Chevrolet, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - City Hall, Cedar Rapids, Iowa, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - Corn Crib #3, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - Corn Crib Near Newburg, Iowa, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - Dubuque From 11th Avenue Bluff, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Dubuque From East Dubuque, Illinois, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - Dubuque From Mount Carmel, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - Edge of Town, La Motte, Iowa, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 4, Folder 38)
      - Farmhouse Interior, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - Farmscape #2, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Farmscape #3, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 5, Folder 41)
      - Feed Coop, McGregor, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      - Iowa #195 (Dried Corn Rows), 2005, printed 2008 (Box 5, Folder 43)
      - Iowa Interstate, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      - Kent Chapel, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 5, Folder 45)
      - Kent Chapel Interior, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 5, Folder 46)
      - Lattnerville Church #1, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - Lattnerville Church #2, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 5, Folder 48)
      - Limestone Barn, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 5, Folder 49)
      - Limestone House, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 5, Folder 50)
      - Main Street, McGregor, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 6, Folder 51)
      - Malcolm Grain Elevator, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 6, Folder 52)
      - Mississippi River at Harper's Slough, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 6, Folder 53)
      - Motor Mill #4, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 6, Folder 54)
      - Norske Lutheran Church, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 6, Folder 55)
      - Oak Trees, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 6, Folder 56)
      - Overgrown Farmhouse, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 6, Folder 57)
      - Pasture #1, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 6, Folder 58)
      - Pasture #2, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 6, Folder 59)
      - Pasture #4, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 6, Folder 60)
      - Pharmacy, Guthrie Center, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 7, Folder 61)
      - Raffety Barn Interior, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 7, Folder 62)
      - Ross Grain Elevator, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 7, Folder 63)
      - St. Joseph's of the Prairie #1, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 7, Folder 64)
      - St. Peter and Paul, Petersburg, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 7, Folder 65)
      - Stennett Grain Elevator #2, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 7, Folder 66)
      - Stennett Grain Elevator #3, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 7, Folder 67)
      - Storm at Dusk, 2005, printed 2009 (Box 7, Folder 68)
      - Tanke Farmhouse, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 7, Folder 69)
      - VanDyke Farm, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 7, Folder 70)
      - View South from B & B Farms, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 8, Folder 71)
      - Wagon, Raffety Farm, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 8, Folder 72)
      - Walnut and 2nd St., Atlantic, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 8, Folder 73)
      - Waukee Grain Elevator #1, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 8, Folder 74)
      - Youngbird Barn interior, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - 2006
      - 1930's Bulldozer, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 8, Folder 76)
      - 350th Avenue, Poweshiek County, Iowa, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 8, Folder 77)
      - Arment Cow Barn Interior, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 8, Folder 78)
      - Arment Horse Barn, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 8, Folder 79)
      - Barn Near Gibson, Iowa, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 8, Folder 80)
      - Barn, Washington County, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 9, Folder 81)
      - Bean Field, Taintor, 2006, printed 2007 (Box 9, Folder 82)
      - Blairstown Feed Mill, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 9, Folder 83)
      - Corn Crib, Circa 1905, 2006, printed 2007 (Box 9, Folder 84)
      - Corn Crib Near Grinnell, Iowa, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 9, Folder 85)
      - Corn Field West of Taintor, Iowa, 2006, printed 2007 (Box 9, Folder 86)
      - Farm West of Grandview, 2006, printed 2007 (Box 9, Folder 87)
      - Farmhouse Near Kinross #1, 2006, printed 2007 (Box 9, Folder 88)
      - Farmhouse on Hill #1, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 9, Folder 89)
      - Farmhouse, 510th Avenue, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 9, Folder 90)
      - Farmscape #6, 2006, printed 2007 (Box 10, Folder 91)
      - Farmscape #7, 2006, printed 2007 (Box 10, Folder 92)
      - Hardware Store, Harper, Iowa, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 10, Folder 93)
      - Hay Field #3, 2006, printed 2007 (Box 10, Folder 94)
      - Hay Field #4, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 10, Folder 95)
      - Hrabak Lumber, Toledo, Iowa, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 10, Folder 96)
      - Iowa #250 (July Corn), 2006, printed 2008 (Box 10, Folder 97)
      - Iowa #619 (Union Pacific Train), 2006, printed 2008 (Box 10, Folder 98)
      - Iowa Landscape #4, 2006, printed 2007 (Box 10, Folder 99)
      - Kellogg Hardware, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 10, Folder 100)
      - Kitchen Sink #2, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 11, Folder 101)
      - Linwood Mining #2, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 11, Folder 102)
      - Livestock Sheds, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 11, Folder 103)
      - Maple Tree Along 450th Avenue #2, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 11, Folder 104)
      - Marengo Co-Op, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 11, Folder 105)
      - Mt. Zion Methodist Church, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 11, Folder 106)
      - Pasture West of Gibson, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 11, Folder 107)
      - Pleasant Hill Cemetery, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 11, Folder 108)
      - Poplar Grove #1, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Poplar Grove #2, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 11, Folder 110)
      - Quaker Oats #1, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 12, Folder 111)
      - Quonsets #1, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 12, Folder 112)
      - Railroad Bridge, 1909, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 12, Folder 113)
      - Remains of Farmstead, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 12, Folder 114)
      - Schoolhouse at Wade Farm #1, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 12, Folder 115)
      - Schoolhouse Door, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 12, Folder 116)
      - Schoolhouse, Washington County, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 12, Folder 117)
      - Sully, Iowa, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 12, Folder 118)
      - Sutherland Station, Marshalltown, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 12, Folder 119)
      - Tavern, Victor Iowa, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 12, Folder 120)
      - Upper Blue Point Cemetery, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 13, Folder 121)
      - Veenstra's, Peoria, Iowa #1, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 13, Folder 122)
      - Veenstra's, Peoria, Iowa #2, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 13, Folder 123)
      - Wall, Chelsea Iowa, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 13, Folder 124)
      - Wild Cherry Tree, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 13, Folder 125)
      - Willow Tree, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 13, Folder 126)
    - 2007
      - Abandoned Farmhouse, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 13, Folder 127)
      - Abandoned Farmhouse #3, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 13, Folder 128)
      - Abandoned Farmhouse #4, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 13, Folder 129)
      - Alexander City Hall, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 13, Folder 130)
      - Barn Interior, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 14, Folder 131)
      - Barn Near Treynor, Iowa, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 14, Folder 132)
      - Canteen, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 14, Folder 133)
      - Cargill, Iowa Falls, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 14, Folder 134)
      - Casey Mill and Elevator #2, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 14, Folder 135)
      - Chicken House, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 14, Folder 136)
      - Chinese Elms, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 14, Folder 137)
      - Corn Crib South of Ladora, Iowa, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 14, Folder 138)
      - Early Summer Field, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 14, Folder 139)
      - Farm North of Perry, Iowa, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 14, Folder 140)
      - Farm North of Perry, Iowa, #2, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 15, Folder 141)
      - Farmhouse North of Ladora #1, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 15, Folder 142)
      - Farmhouse North of Ladora #3, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 15, Folder 143)
      - Farmscape #8, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 15, Folder 144)
      - Farmscape #10, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 15, Folder 145)
      - Farmstead, Franklin County #1, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 15, Folder 146)
      - Fence #2, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 15, Folder 147)
      - Ferguson Elevator #1, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 15, Folder 148)
      - Ferguson Elevator #2, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 15, Folder 149)
      - Ferguson Elevator #3, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 15, Folder 150)
      - Gate, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 16, Folder 151)
      - Grain Elevator, Elk Horn #1, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 16, Folder 152)
      - High View Farm #2, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 16, Folder 153)
      - Iowa #109, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 16, Folder 154)
      - Iowa #235, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 16, Folder 155)
      - Iowa #789, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 16, Folder 156)
      - Iowa #800 (Gravel Road), 2007, printed 2008 (Box 16, Folder 157)
      - Iowa #815, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 16, Folder 158)
      - Iowa #886 (Diner Window), 2007, printed 2008 (Box 16, Folder 159)
      - Iowa #1357 (New Corn, Sunlight), 2007, printed 2008 (Box 16, Folder 160)
      - Iowa #1418 (Layered Hills), 2007, printed 2008 (Box 17, Folder 161)
      - Iowa #1462 (Red Barn), 2007, printed 2008 (Box 17, Folder 162)
      - Iowa #1532 (Prairie), 2007, printed 2008 (Box 17, Folder 163)
      - Iowa Landscape #6, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 17, Folder 164)
      - Iowa Landscape #7, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 17, Folder 165)
      - Iowa Landscape #10, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 17, Folder 166)
      - Iowa Landscape #11, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 17, Folder 167)
      - Kent Chapel #3, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 17, Folder 168)
      - Leaning Tree, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 17, Folder 169)
      - Lincoln Township Hall, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 17, Folder 170)
      - Maysville Schoolhouse, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 18, Folder 171)
      - Meyer Farm, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 18, Folder 172)
      - Moon at Sunset, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 18, Folder 173)
      - New Corn and Shadow, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 18, Folder 174)
      - New Grain Bins, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 18, Folder 175)
      - Pasture Near Exira, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 18, Folder 176)
      - Pasture, Tama County, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 18, Folder 177)
      - Pharmacy, Guthrie Center #2, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 18, Folder 178)
      - Pioneer Cemetery, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 18, Folder 179)
      - Purdum Farm #3, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 18, Folder 180)
      - Purdum Farm #4, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 19, Folder 181)
      - Railroad Crossing, Newburg, Iowa, #1, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 19, Folder 182)
      - Stringtown Cemetery, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 19, Folder 183)
      - Swing, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 19, Folder 184)
      - Three Tires, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 19, Folder 185)
      - Towne Farm, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 19, Folder 186)
      - Train Car, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 19, Folder 187)
      - Twisting Barn, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 19, Folder 188)
      - Union Pacific, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 19, Folder 189)
      - What Cheer Opera House #4, 2007, printed 2010 (Box 19, Folder 190)
      - Windbreak, 2007, printed 2010 (Box 20, Folder 191)
    - 2008
      - Barn and Ash Tree, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 20, Folder 192)
      - Barn and Corn Fields, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 20, Folder 193)
      - Barn, Poweshiek County, Iowa, 2008, printed 2010 (Box 20, Folder 194)
      - Bean Field During Storm, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 20, Folder 195)
      - Church Grounds, Haverhill, Iowa, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 20, Folder 196)
      - Clark's Bar, Melbourne, Iowa, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 20, Folder 197)
      - Crops in Mist, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 20, Folder 198)
      - Distributor Control, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 20, Folder 199)
      - Eden Township Hall #1, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 20, Folder 200)
      - Elevator at Beaman, Iowa, #1, 2008, printed 2010 (Box 21, Folder 201)
      - Elevator at Sully, Iowa, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 21, Folder 202)
      - Elevator West of Beaman, Iowa, #1, 2008, printed 2010 (Box 21, Folder 203)
      - Ervin Barn #2, 2008, printed 2010 (Box 21, Folder 204)
      - Farm East of Peoria, Illinois, 2008, printed 2010 (Box 21, Folder 205)
      - Farmhouse on 110th St., 2008, printed 2010 (Box 21, Folder 206)
      - Farmhouse South of Nevada, Iowa, 2008, printed 2010 (Box 21, Folder 207)
      - Gillroy Feed #1, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 21, Folder 208)
      - Hanna Cemetery, 2008, printed 2010 (Box 21, Folder 209)
      - House Renovation, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 21, Folder 210)
      - Lyle Creek, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 22, Folder 211)
      - Mailbox Along Road, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 22, Folder 212)
      - Mid Iowa Coop, Haverhill, Iowa, 2008, printed 2010 (Box 22, Folder 213)
      - Pella Feed Service, 2008, printed 2010 (Box 22, Folder 214)
      - Poll Dairy Farm #2, 2008, printed 2010 (Box 22, Folder 215)
      - Power Lines, Mahaska County, Iowa, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 22, Folder 216)
      - Renovation, Franklin, Iowa, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 22, Folder 217)
      - Sheppler Barber Shop #1, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 22, Folder 218)
      - Sheppler Barber Shop #2, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 22, Folder 219)
      - Sheppler Barber Shop #3, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 22, Folder 220)
      - Sheppler Barber Shop #4, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 23, Folder 221)
      - Sheppler Barber Shop #5, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 23, Folder 222)
      - Silos and Barn Near West Point, 2008, printed 2010 (Box 23, Folder 223)
      - St. Andrew's Lutheran, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 23, Folder 224)
      - St. Donatus Church, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 23, Folder 225)
      - Sterling Cemetery #1, 2008, printed 2010 (Box 23, Folder 226)
      - Sterling Cemetery #2, 2008, printed 2010 (Box 23, Folder 227)
    - 2009
      - Abandoned House, 510th Avenue, 2009, printed 2009 (Box 23, Folder 228)
      - Bedroom, 2009, printed 2010 (Box 23, Folder 229)
      - Cloud Over Winter Field, 2009, printed 2009 (Box 23, Folder 230)
      - Delta Grocery, 2009, printed 2010 (Box 24, Folder 231)
      - Dolls, 2009, printed 2010 (Box 24, Folder 232)
      - Edge of Corn Field, 2009, printed 2010 (Box 24, Folder 233)
      - Iowa State Capitol, 2009, printed 2009 (Box 24, Folder 234)
      - Kent Chapel, Kitchen Door, 2009, printed 2009 (Box 24, Folder 235)
      - Poplar Grove, 2009, printed 2010 (Box 24, Folder 236)
      - Rolling Landscape, 2009, printed 2010 (Box 24, Folder 237)
      - Schoolhouse, Wade Farm, 2009, printed 2009 (Box 24, Folder 238)
      - Shed #1, B & B Farms, 2009, printed 2010 (Box 24, Folder 239)
      - Soldiers and Sailors Memorial, 2009, printed 2009 (Box 24, Folder 240)
      - Wind Farm, Story County, Iowa, 2009, printed 2010 (Box 25, Folder 241)
    - 2010
      - Barn, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 25, Folder 242)
      - Delicate Fence, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 25, Folder 243)
      - Ethanol Plant, Grand Junction, Iowa, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 25, Folder 244)
      - Farmhouse at Sunset, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 25, Folder 245)
      - Grain Bin, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 25, Folder 246)
      - Hay Wagons, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 25, Folder 247)
      - North 75th Avenue East, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 25, Folder 248)
      - Richland Creek, Winter, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 25, Folder 249)
      - Seed Factory, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 25, Folder 250)
      - Shed #2, B & B Farms, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 26, Folder 251)
      - Snow Drift, Fence, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 26, Folder 252)
      - Snowscape, Marshall County, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 26, Folder 253)
      - Snowscape, Tama County, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 26, Folder 254)
      - Snowscape, Tama County, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 26, Folder 255)
      - Superior Grain Bin, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 26, Folder 256)
      - Tires, B & B Farms, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 26, Folder 257)
      - Winter Fields, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 26, Folder 258)
      - Yard, Ogden, Iowa, 2010, printed 2010 (Box 26, Folder 259)
  - 16" X 20" Prints
    - 2004
      - Downey Grain Elevator, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 27, Folder 260)
      - Kitchen, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 27, Folder 261)
      - Ladora Savings Bank #1, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 27, Folder 262)
      - Stone Farmhouse #1, 2004, printed 2007 (Box 27, Folder 263)
    - 2005
      - Elkport #1, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 27, Folder 264)
      - Farmscape #4, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 27, Folder 265)
      - McGregor Grain Elevator, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 27, Folder 266)
      - Motor Mill #1, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 27, Folder 267)
      - St. Joseph's of the Prairie #2, 2005, printed 2007 (Box 27, Folder 268)
      - Hawkeye Ethanol Plant #1, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 27, Folder 269)
      - Hawkeye Ethanol Plant #2, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 28, Folder 270)
      - Hawkeye Ethanol Plant #3, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 28, Folder 271)
      - Hawkeye Ethanol Plant #4, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 28, Folder 272)
      - Hawkeye Ethanol Plant #5, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 28, Folder 273)
      - Motor Mill #2, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 28, Folder 274)
      - Motor Mill #3, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 28, Folder 275)
      - Rockwell Five Star Co-op #3, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 28, Folder 276)
      - Stennett Grain Elevator #1, 2005, printed 2008 (Box 28, Folder 277)
    - 2006
      - 4 County Coop, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 28, Folder 278)
      - Feed Coop, Barnes City #1, 2006, printed 2008 (Box 28, Folder 279)
      - Iowa Landscape #5, 2006, printed 2007 (Box 29, Folder 280)
      - Pasture North of Millersburg, 2006, printed 2007 (Box 29, Folder 281)
      - Poplar Grove #3, 2006, printed 2007 (Box 29, Folder 282)
      - Schoolhouse at Wade Farm #2, 2006, printed 2007 (Box 29, Folder 283)
    - 2007
      - Barn and Windmill, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 29, Folder 284)
      - Crib With Hay Bales #1, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 29, Folder 285)
      - Egg Factory, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 29, Folder 286)
      - Elevator, Beaver, Iowa, 2007, printed 2010 (Box 29, Folder 287)
      - Elevator, Dexter, Iowa, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 29, Folder 288)
      - Farmhouse on Hill #3, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 29, Folder 289)
      - Farmscape #9, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 30, Folder 290)
      - Farmstead, East of Laurel, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 30, Folder 291)
      - Ferguson Elevator #4, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 30, Folder 292)
      - Hay Bales, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 30, Folder 293)
      - House on Meskwak Road #1, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 30, Folder 294)
      - Iowa Landscape #8, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 30, Folder 295)
      - Iowa Landscape #9, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 30, Folder 296)
      - Maple and Walnut Trees, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 30, Folder 297)
      - Oak Trees in Pasture, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 30, Folder 298)
      - St. Patrick's Church, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 30, Folder 299)
      - Two Barns, Calhoun County, 2007, printed 2008 (Box 31, Folder 300)
      - What Cheer Clay Products #2, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 31, Folder 301)
      - Willow Tree #2, 2007, printed 2009 (Box 31, Folder 302)
    - 2008
      - Barn West of Newburg, Iowa, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 31, Folder 303)
      - Broadway and High Street, Toledo, Ohio, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 31, Folder 304)
      - Farm Near Goose Lake, Iowa, 2008, printed 2010 (Box 31, Folder 305)
      - Felderman Farm, St. Donatus #2, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 31, Folder 306)
      - Gillroy Feed #2, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 31, Folder 307)
      - Iowa Landscape #14, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 31, Folder 308)
      - Monsanto, Near Grinnell, Iowa, 2008, printed 2009 (Box 31, Folder 309)